Everyone knows you can't study on an empty stomach.
Hi, I'm Alexa Sparkman, and today we're going to talk about healthy dorm room snacking.
When you've got the munchies it's really easy to reach for the high fat, high sugar options.
Today, we're going to talk about something that might be a little bit more healthy.
Of course, popcorn is a good late night snack, and, any more, you can even buy a hundred calorie packs of microwave popcorn.
Hot chocolate on a cold winters night is a good option, having a few packs in the dorm room is quick and easy.
All you have to do is add hot water.
And then, we've always got the carrot and ranch dip snack, it's nice to keep a few things on hand when you've got those crunchy munchies.
There are, also, some sweet options when the sweet tooth hits.
Consider, when you're choosing cookies, those that are high in fiber and low in fat.
If you're trying to find a meal replacement, there are plenty of bar options out there, if you're running between class, and you know you're not going to make it back for a meal in the cafeteria, consider the meal replacement bars.
Or, if you just need a little snack, trail mix bars are a good option when you're on the go.
And that's how you eat healthy dorm room snacks.
I'm Alexa Sparkman until next time.